let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is an Exoplanet?",
    answer: "A planet outside our solar system",
    options: [
      "A planet in our solar syatem",
      "A planet outside our solar system",
      "A star that orbits the sun",
      "One of earths moon"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the name of the method used to discover many exoplanets?",
    answer: "Transit method",
    options: [
      "Transit method",
      "Gravitational pull method",
      "Direct imaging",
      "Exploration"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is the habitable zone?",
    answer: "The region around a star where a planet could have liquid water",
    options: [
      "The region around a star where a planet could have liquid water",
      "The area of space where stars and planets form",
      "The region around a star where planets are too hot to support life",
      "A region very far away from the sun"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which telescope has helped discover many exoplanets?",
    answer: "Kepler Space Telescope",
    options: [
      "James Webb Space ",
      "Galilean Telescope",
      "Hubble Space Telescope",
      "Kepler Space Telescope"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is one of the key ingredients for life that scientists look for on exoplanets?",
    answer: "Liquid water",
    options: [
      "Liquid water",
      "Lava",
      "Methane",
      "Oxygen"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "How do scientists detect the wobble of a star to find exoplanets?",
    answer: "By measuring shifts in the star’s light spectrum",
    options: [
      "By measuring shifts in the star’s light spectrum ",
      " By observing the star’s color changes",
      "By measuring the star’s temperature",
      "By finding out the star's age"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What type of planet is a gas giant like Jupiter?",
    answer: "A large planet with no solid surface",
    options: [
      " A small, rocky planet",
      "A large planet with no solid surface",
      " A planet with water oceans and landmasses",
      "A planet closest to the sun"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What does it mean if a planet is in the ‘habitable zone’?",
    answer: "It is in a region where liquid water might exist",
    options: [
      "It has an atmosphere like Earth’s",
      " It is close enough to its star to melt ice",
      "It is in a region where liquid water might exist",
      "It has its own moon"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What do scientists use space telescopes for when studying exoplanets?",
    answer: "To measure a planet’s size, temperature, and atmosphere",
    options: [
      " To see the exoplanets directly with visible light",
      "To measure a planet’s size, temperature, and atmosphere",
      "To find comets near the planet",
      "To look at satellites"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is one of the key goals of exoplanet exploration?",
    answer: "To discover planets that could support life?",
    options: [
      " To find stars that are close to Earth",
      " To discover planets that could support life",
      "To study black holes near planets",
      "To send man to space"
    ]
  },
  
];
